So, how much power did you add ?
Don't be surprised, Keisuke.
It's got 260 hp at the maximum.
You dropped it from 340 hp ?!
What's the point of slowing the car down ?
You must've learned the lesson
the hard way after you raced him.
Total balance is the key to
mastering the downhill, not power.
Sometimes you have to lower the power to go
faster, which makes street racing complex.
So Akina's Eight-Six is a formidable opponent ?
You could say that.
I was confident I could manage big power on the
downhill, so this de-tune is humiliating.
I have to put my pride aside in order to win.
Incredible. The exit speed at
the corners is definitely faster.
There's another reason
why I dropped the FC's power.
If I just out-power the Eight-Six on
the straightaways, that's not a victory.
That won't satisfy me.
Technique against technique.
Drift against drift. That's my way.
I'm happy to have met a driver
who makes me feel this way.
I feel like I've changed back to Akagi's White
Comet, instead of Takahashi Ryosuke of the Red
Suns.
Brother...